http://www.quotemedia.com/legal/privacy/

QuoteMedia Company
QuoteMedia (PPT)
Web Content (PPT)
Contact QuoteMedia
Questions?
Contact QuoteMedia
Questions?
Contact QuoteMedia
Questions?
Contact QuoteMedia
Questions?
1. PRIVACY POLICY
1.1 QuoteMedia is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of users of it's interactive products and services.
1.2 This privacy policy applies to the QuoteMedia.com Inc. site and all of the Internet accessible QuoteMedia branded services, which we may offer from time to time, referred hereinafter as QuoteMedia. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, our visitor, what types of information we may gather about you when visiting our site and how we may use that information. We will also inform you whether we disclose your information to anyone and if so, under what conditions, as well as the choices you have regarding our use of the information.
1.3 In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information, such as; numbers and frequency of visitors to QuoteMedia and the areas visited. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use various areas of the site, so we can improve our site.
1.4 QuoteMedia cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are. Most browsers are set to accept cookies. You can set yours to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so please note that some part of our site may not function properly.
1.5 We may provide information to other partners about how our members use QuoteMedia. We do this to provide you the best Web experience possible and to improve the site in general.
1.6 Our site's registration forms require contact information (like name and email address) and demographic information (like zip code, age, and income level). We will not disclose your personal information to any third party advertisers unless we are compelled by law or, in our sole discretion, whenever we believe an emergency, illegal activity or some other reasonable basis exists for notifying or providing such information to the appropriate authorities. We reserve the right, directly or through our designated marketing agents, to distribute promotional materials to you for QuoteMedia products or for products of our marketing partners. Such promotions will be for products believed to be of interest to our user base. Your personal information shall remain in the possession of QuoteMedia or its designated marketing agent at all times. We sometimes aggregate information about our users and you agree we can use and make such statistical information available to others, as long as we don't identify you personally. QuoteMedia gives users the option to opt out or discontinue promotional communications from (a) within promotional emails, and/or (b) within the registration area of each QuoteMedia website or web based application. In addition, to stop receiving special announcements from QuoteMedia, users can email unsubscribe@quotemedia.com and type UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line.
1.7 Your personal information may be stored and/or processed or otherwise used by or on behalf of QuoteMedia both inside the United States and Canada.
Your personal information may be processed and stored in a country that has laws that are different from those in your jurisdiction, and where the government (e.g. the United States or Canada) may be able to obtain disclosure of your personal information under their local laws.
2. USE OF COOKIES
A cookie is a very small text file placed on your hard drive by a Web Page server. It is essentially your identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. It is uniquely yours and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. Our service may place one or more cookies on your computer. These cookies may be used to remind us who you are and what features or premium services you have registered for or to estimate our audience size and target marketing based on user interest. Advertisers on Our Service may also use cookies. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1x1 pixel .gif technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt out or visit the National Advertising Initiative ("NAI") gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network-advertising cookies. Click here for the NAI gateway opt-out. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies' privacy policies. If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us by clicking here.
3. LINKS TO OTHER SITES AND PRIVACY
3.1 Users will find advertising or other content on our site that link to a site or services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors, and other third parties. In many cases, the links represent cooperative projects or are mutual links established with persons or entities connected with our site. Although we initially visit the sites or services that are so linked, we do not control the contents or links that appear on these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their contents and links may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies or no policy at all, as such; we accept no liability for their policies.
3.2 We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use session information (this information does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp
4. CREDIT CARD SECURITY/PRIVACY POLICY
Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority. We have taken careful measures to secure both your information and our premises. We exercise great care in the transfer of information from your PC to our servers. Our credit card secure sever software encrypts information, ensuring that all Internet credit card transactions remain private.
5. POLICY CHANGES
Should we make changes to our privacy policy or disclaimer we will post such changes under the appropriate heading, here on our site, so that you will always know what information we gather and how we might use that information.
6. RELEASE OF INFORMATION
We will release specific information about you, or your account, to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order.
7. ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS
By using the QuoteMedia site you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy and Disclaimer. If you do not agree to this policy or disclaimer please do not use the site. Your continued use of the QuoteMedia site following the posting of any subsequent changes to these terms will mean that you have accepted such changes. Questions regarding our privacy statement and disclaimer may be directed to info@quotemedia.com.
8. REVISION
Last revision date: September 9, 2014
Copyright © 2020 QuoteMedia, Inc.
